Deciding to create my own website was difficult for some reasons.
Firstly, there was a very vivid negative experience several years ago
when we got something completely different from what we wanted and
for a very large sum of money. Secondly, I thought that if I really
tried, I could build the website myself. But then the need for a
website outweighed all other doubts and fears, and we started working
with the RedSquirrel team. Ease of communication, full understanding
of the task, and clarity in work - that's exactly what I needed at the
first stage. Help in structuring all my "must-have" and "not necessary"
items, advice, and professional recommendations from the heads of the
team helped me clearly understand how the website would look after
just 1 day! It was nice that everything was done on time, without
reminders and postponements. And when, after a few days, I already
saw the first ready pages of the website...I must admit, I didn't even
believe it was my website! The online store was created very quickly -
that's awesome! Thank you for the work! For making the website
convenient and understandable for customers, for excellent
communication, and for turning the website development into a
pleasant pastime. Towards the end, it was even a little sad to part
ways :) When the work is awesome - it shows! You have it just like that!
Once again, heartfelt thanks for the website and for the work!
Wishing you creative success and more clients!