We have been working together for several years now, and are satisfied
with the work, as they are highly qualified specialists. Now, let's
discuss everything in order: Our team has been involved in website
development for 17 years and, of course, has a clear understanding of
what a specialist responsible for the promotion of the main site
should do. We placed ads on several platforms to find a specialist
and conduct a paid audit. Mostly, potential candidates sent poorly
qualified explanations. At this stage, Ekaterina stood out from the
list of all candidates by identifying a small, yet significant bug on
our site. At the start of our collaboration, we and Ekaterina's team
conducted a site audit. We thoroughly analyzed all the indicators
that could affect the site's ranking. We compiled a huge list of
activities for improvements in design, coding, and site usability,
which we methodically implemented over the year. Ekaterina managed to
form a team of competent technical specialists who are involved in
the development of the site, so I especially want to acknowledge
Ekaterina's contribution as a project manager. Lastly, we would like
to mention an important quality of Ekaterina as a specialist in a
competitive environment. She continuously attends webinars and
courses and engages in themed communities, which allows her to stay
up-to-date with the latest technologies and enhance her knowledge, and
as a consequence, provide invaluable assistance. We look forward to
years of fruitful cooperation and moving only forward.