Our online school of landscape design will turn three years old in
the summer of 2022. We have been working with Alena and her team for
nearly a year and a half. They are the ones who create all our
landing pages and websites, which I associate with the success of our
school. Before starting work with RedSquirrel, at least six people
failed to meet our expectations. My first work contact with the Red
Squirrel team impressed me with their systematic approach and clear
organization of labor. Later, I was convinced that they had delved so
deeply into our subject matter that it sometimes seemed as though the
team members could read my thoughts. It is pleasing that today, in
the frantic pace of hustle and bustle, there are people you can rely
on to work through all the details and find new solutions and
algorithms for improving and systematizing business. Work is always
on time, attention to detail, strict adherence to specifications,
nearly 24-hour feedback, prompt responses, and keeping up with the
day's trends. These qualities seem rare today. That is exactly why I
recommended the RedSquirrel team to my daughter Olesya, who has her
own small business making women's jewelry. I want to express my deep
gratitude to Alena and the RedSquirrel team for their approach to
clients and wish them success in a very important aspect of any
business - creating the "face" of your enterprise and your
recognizability.