Our fruitful collaboration with Ekaterina and the RedSquirrel team
began when we needed to create a professional-looking and functional
website for the humanitarian organization laruhelpsukraine.com. After
discussing the mission and goals of the organization, they started
working on the site structure, preparing prototypes, and drawing the
design of the main and step-by-step next pages. After agreeing on the
design, they began working on layout and development in cooperation
with the programmers. Ekaterina supported the organization and
actively participated in its work for a long time, adapting flexibly
to changing goals and priorities. They effectively implemented the
necessary changes and improvements on the site and also provided
tangible assistance in training employees to work with the site.
Ekaterina and her team work in a very structured way, clearly
pronounce priorities and independently coordinate the development and
implementation of the website within the agreed time frame. She asks
for feedback in a timely manner and provides the necessary
recommendations and support in making decisions. Ekaterina is a
pleasure to work with and she has excellent taste. We were completely
satisfied with the work performed by the RedSquirrel team.