I'm not good at SEO, but Ekaterina was extremely clear and
straightforward with me. I really appreciate honesty when I see it in
specialists. I was very satisfied with the service offered by
Ekaterina and her team.  They are professionals who show me the way to
improve the SEO for my website and the website of my clients. I would
totally recommend working with them because of quality of work, fast
delivery, precision, empathy and understanding of difficult
situations. They also agreed to give me a specific report, and they
are very fast learning about operations in a web marketing agency.
Thank you to the RedSquirrel team, we will work surely again. Best
SEO experts I had till now.  Strongly recommended.