(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Our online School of Landscape Design will turn three years
old in the summer of 2022. We have been working with Alina
and her team for nearly a year and a half. They are the
ones who create all our landing pages and websites, which I
associate with the success of our school.  Before starting
work with Red Squirrel, at least six people failed to meet
our expectations. My first work contact with the Red
Squirrel team impressed me with their systematic approach
and clear organization of labor. Later, I was convinced
that they had delved so deeply into our subject matter that
it sometimes seemed as though the team members could read
my thoughts.  It is pleasing that today, in the frantic pace
of hustle and bustle, there are people you can rely on to
work through all the details and find new solutions and
algorithms for improving and systematizing business. Work
is always on time, attention to detail, strict adherence to
specifications, nearly 24-hour feedback, prompt responses,
and keeping up with the day's trends. These qualities seem
rare today.  That is exactly why I recommended the Red
Squirrel team to my daughter, Olesya, who has her own small
business making women's jewelry. I want to express my deep
gratitude to Elena and the Red Squirrel team for their
approach to clients and wish them success in a very
important aspect of any business, creating the face of your
enterprise and your recognizability.